One step can change your world.
Step Up Revolution is a music, drama, romance film directed by Scott Speer.
Emily arrives in Miami with aspirations to become a professional dancer.
She sparks with Sean, the leader of a dance crew whose neighborhood
is threatened by Emily's father's development plans.
Emily Anderson, played by Kathryn McCormick.
Sean Asa, played by Ryan Guzman.
Eddy, played by Misha Gabriel.
Jason Hardlerson, played by Stephen 'tWitch' Boss.
DJ Penelope, played by Cleopatra Coleman.
Bill Anderson, played by Peter Gallagher.
Step Up Revolution (released in some countries as Step Up 4: Miami Heat) is a 2012
American dance film directed by Scott Speer and written by Amanda Brody.
The film is the sequel to  Step Up 3D (2010) and the
fourth installment in the Step Up film series.
It stars Ryan Guzman, Kathryn McCormick, Misha Gabriel, Cleopatra Coleman,
Stephen "tWitch" Boss, Tommy Dewey, and Peter Gallagher.
Step Up Revolution was released in the United States on July 27, 2012, by
Summit Entertainment, through conventional 2D and 3D formats.
It became the first film in the series to not be co-produced by Touchstone Pictures nor distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion
Pictures and the first film to be released by Summit after being acquired by Lions Gate Entertainment in January 2012.
The film grossed over $140 million against a production budget of
$33 million and received mixed reviews from critics.
A sequel, Step Up: All In, was released in August 2014 in the United States.
The film explores themes of duringcreditsstinger, flash mob, dance
instructor, real estate development, dance company.
The tone is emotional.